

Seoul, Republic of Korea

□ (+82) 10-5577-5814 | ■ newinh90@gmail.com | ♠ newinh.me | 回 newinh | 🖹 newinh | 🗖

Summary_

3+ year experience in back-end development.

Open culture of IT industry was so impressive that I started developmenting software. As I got help and inspired, I want to be a engineer who can help. Main skills are Python, django, flask, MySQL now, but I'm ready to challenge other technical skills and accomplish projects.

Skills_

Programming Python

Frameworks Django, Flask, Scrapy, pandas

Infrastructures AWS, Docker, MySQL

Languages Korea(native), English(Business)

Work Experience

Kasa Korea Co., Ltd. Seoul, S.Korea

BACK-END ENGINEER Jul. 2019 - Sep. 2021

Kasa Service Web Server.

- Contributed project from scratch and experienced in early stages of operation.
- · Implemented Authentication, Public Offering, Ledger services. Designed entity-relation and REST API.
- Django, DRF, MySQL, redis

Omnious. Co., Ltd. Seoul, S.Korea

Back-end Engineer Nov. 2017 - Jul. 2019

Labeling Tool

- Maintained back-end of in-house web application having 50+ active users for collecting fashion data to train AI model.
 - Docker, CircleCI, Rancher, AWS(EC2, S3, RDS)
- Designed RESTful HTTP API, developed server serving them. Documented API specification for communication.
 - flask, NGINX, uWSGI, Swagger
- Established relation of domain model, designed database schema.
 - MySQL
- Built HTTP access logging system and pipeline to store it.
 - fluntd, fluent-bit
- Introduced unit testing, style guide of codebase.
 - flake8, pytest

Data Extraction & Transformation

- Extracted collected data to train AI model and pre-processed in a form that is easy to train.
- Automated process from data extraction to data processing, developed CLI tool to access automated data transfer system.
- pandas, Celery

Crawler

- · Implemented 20+ web crawlers for collecting fashion images, developed a scheduling tool for management.
- Built serverless pipeline that stores crawled data in a storage.
- Scrapy, ScrapingHub, Zappa, AWS(SNS, SQS, Labmda)

LayGen Inc. Gyeonggi-do, S.Korea

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN

Aug. 2017 - Sep. 2017

- Participated to manufactoring operating module for a prototype of 3D printer and developed software control the module.
- Developed GUI so that hardware engineer can test controling each part of 3D printer.
- Python, PyQT, Rasberry Pi, Arduino

LINE Corp. *Gyeonggi-do, S.Korea, S.Korea*

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN

Apr. 2017 - May. 2017

- Prototyped iOS application "Targeted Video" emphasizing object user want in video.
- Used technique of contour extraction, image segmentation and stabilization.
- Implemented video editing function that cuts or pastes object user selected.
- Swift, OpenCV

Education

BoostCamp, Connect Foundation education program

Seoul, S.Korea

iOS Course Jan. 2017 - Feb. 2017

Developed iOS Application, "Color to Sound, Sound to Color! ChromaTone"
 https://github.com/newinh/ChromaTone

Konkuk University Seoul, S.Korea

B.S. IN ELECTRONICS

Mar. 2009 - Feb. 2016

• Graduation piece, "IOT Door Lock using Wireless Home Router & Android Device"